I'm so very happy that you've reached this epic moment in the course and that you're hanging in there.
에픽이 이 역사적인 순간에 도달해서 정말 기뻐요 끝까지 버틴 것도요
This is where things have gotten really crucial, and we're learning some of the most important things
아주 중요한 부분입니다 LMS 구축에 가장 중요한 것들을
about building an LMS.
배우고 있죠
And I'm I'm just very grateful that you've been staying along and hopefully enjoying it as much as I
계속 함께해 줘서 정말 고마워요 나만큼 이곳을 즐기면 좋겠네요
And yeah, the best is yet to come.
네, 아직 최고의 순간은 오지 않았어요
So, uh, for today, it's going to be few slides.
오늘은 슬라이드를 몇 개 보여드릴게요
It's going to be all action.
액션이 가득할 거예요
Uh, you're going to be looking at the actual run happening and weights and biases, and I'll be showing
당신은 실제 경기 상황을 보고 무게와 편향성을 살펴볼 거예요 저는 그런 것들을 살펴보고
you the sorts of things to look for and how we can use weights and biases to get some intelligence about
무게와 편향성을 어떻게 이용하면 경기 결과를 알 수 있는지 보여 드릴게요 get
what's happening.
it
Uh, I'm going to show you the Huggingface hub with models in it, and you get a sense of what's going
먼저 허깅페이스 허브를 보여드릴게요 모델들이 있어요 어떤 상황인지 아실
on.
거예요
Um, there's also one thing that's been on my mind that I mentioned last time that I, I don't want
지난번에 말씀드렸던 것 중에 마음에 걸리는 게 하나 있는데 경솔하게 가격을
to be flippant about the importance of keeping costs low.
낮추는 게 얼마나 중요한지 말하고 싶지 않아요
The idea of this class is not to build up a big bill for you from, uh, from Google, who will happily
이 수업의 목적은 구글로부터 거액의 청구서를 받는 게 아닙니다 구글은
take your, your money for for running their boxes.
여러분의 돈을 기꺼이 받아 가겠죠
Um, I have a lot of fun running this training.
이 훈련이 정말 재밌어요
It's, um, running the training process.
훈련 과정을 진행하는 거죠
Um, it's perfectly achievable to do that and get good results with the spending a matter of cents.
Get it은 완벽하게 가능합니다 단돈 센트로 좋은 결과를 낼 수 있죠
And I did want to take just a quick moment to talk about that, because it's very important.
잠시 그 얘길 하고 싶었어요 아주 중요하니까요
And I don't want to, uh, lead you down the wrong path of thinking you have to spend lots of money
잘못된 길로 인도하고 싶진 않아요 많은 돈을 써야 좋은 결과를 얻고 배우게
to get good results and to learn particularly, which is the main objective here.
된다는 생각을요 그게 주된 목표죠 get a my life
Um, and so, in fact, we're going to start with that.
그래서 거기서부터 시작할 거예요
Um, and I want to, uh, take you straight over to JupyterLab, not not to Google Colab, but JupyterLab,
유피터랩으로 바로 안내하겠습니다 구글 콜랍이 아니라 유피터랩입니다 제 주장을
where I'm going to show you something to illustrate my point and to help set you up should you wish
설명하고 더 저렴한 가격에 훈련하고 싶다면 설정하는 데 도움이
to be training at a lower cost.
될 뭔가를 보여드릴게요